Jaydeep Das

Product Designer

1309 Tagore Park, Nashkarhat, Kolkata

9874943709

jaydeepdas06@gmail.com

https://jay.deep261994.github.io/jay.deepdasui.github.io/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a Product Designer with a Bachelors degree in Fine Arts. Currently as a product designer, I would want to contribute to the complete project life cycle from the ideation phase to the implementation phase and also managing the same, focused on creating meaningful experiences through design.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Creative Head Kolkata, Agpaytech Pvt. Ltd. September 2020 - Present

Formalized a team within Central Design to deliver a distributed-yet-centralized Design System. Defined the roadmap, roles and responsibilities, and ways of working. Developed a culture of contribution in order to scale. Delivered a unified set of guidelines, toolkits, and accessible components for the legacy product <u>ATL Money Transfer</u> and Remitall mobile and web platform . Art directed a small design team that handled seasonal campaign material.

Graphic Designer Gunjaan App Studio

Oct 2019 - August 2020

Designed various design projects for various products including graphic design, storyboard and game templats for kids.

Junior Game Designer iPApps Technologies Pvt Ltd July 2019 - Oct 2019

Worked for multiple games creating including design, layout design, illustration, typography, and character design.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Sarbabharatiya Sangeet O Sanskriti Parishad Bachelor in Fine Arts 2019

University of Calcutta
Bachelor of Commerce
2020
Accounting and Finance

OTHER EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Google UX Design Professional Certificate Coursera, 2020

SKILLS

Methods

3D Design Accessible Design Wireframing Rapid Prototyping

Tools

Unity

Adobe Suite (Photoshop, XD, Illustrator,

After Effects)

Cinema 4D **Technical**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript